We all make choices. What's yours?
The Last Kiss is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Tony Goldwyn.
Michael has a great job, has his 4 best friends, and is
in love with a beautiful girl at 30.
He loves Jenna but his life seems predictable
until someone else enters his life.
It seems that everybody's having relationship problems.
Michael, played by Zach Braff.
Jenna, played by Jacinda Barrett.
Chris, played by Casey Affleck.
Kim, played by Rachel Bilson.
Izzy, played by Michael Weston.
Kenny, played by Eric Christian Olsen.
The Last Kiss is a 2006 American romantic comedy-drama film which is based on
2001 Italian film of the same name, directed by Gabriele Muccino.
The plot revolves around a young couple and their friends struggling
with adulthood and issues of relationships and commitment.
The film stars Zach Braff, Jacinda Barrett, Casey Affleck and Rachel Bilson.
The screenplay was written by Paul Haggis, and directed by Tony Goldwyn.
Much of The Last Kiss was filmed in and around Madison, Wisconsin.
As with Garden State, Braff was involved with the film's soundtrack.
The first teaser trailer was released on Braff's
official website in mid-June 2006.
The film premiered at the Deauville Film Festival and the Toronto International Film Festival on September 10,
2006, and was released by DreamWorks Pictures (through Paramount Pictures) on September 15, 2006.
The film received mixed reviews, and grossed $16
million against a $20 million budget.
The film explores themes of pregnancy, striptease,
architect, deceived wife, stripper.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.